http://www.sputnikmusic.com/policy.php

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us. At Sputnikmusic we have a few fundamental principles:
* We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
* We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
* We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Sputnikmusic collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Sputnikmusic's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Sputnikmusic's visitors use its website. From time to time, Sputnikmusic may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Sputnikmusic also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Sputnikmusic does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.
Gathering of Information
Certain visitors to Sputnikmusic's websites choose to interact with Sputnikmusic in ways that require Sputnikmusic to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Sputnikmusic gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Sputnikmusic collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Sputnikmusic. Sputnikmusic does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Sputnikmusic may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.
Sputnikmusic may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Sputnikmusic does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Information
Sputnikmusic discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Sputnikmusic's behalf or to provide services available at Sputnikmusic's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Sputnikmusic's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Sputnikmusic will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Sputnikmusic discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Sputnikmusic believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sputnikmusic, third parties or the public at large. Sputnikmusic takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Sputnikmusic uses cookies to help Sputnikmusic identify and track visitors, their usage of Sputnikmusic website, and their website access preferences. Sputnikmusic visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Sputnikmusic's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Sputnikmusic's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Sputnikmusic and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Click here to revoke your choice
You may opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link located here
We are participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sputnikmusic may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Sputnikmusic's sole discretion. Sputnikmusic encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
